Guess what. Uncle
Crowley? I'm hungry.
So. Amara's growing
like a radioactive weed?
By stuffing her face with souls.
If she's half as powerful as I
think she is. I want her on my team.
The Darkness is
almost infinite power.
We're bound. Dean.
God kicked this
thing's ass once before.
We need your help. God.
You know who we need
to help with The Darkness.
Hello. Demon Tablet!
He was God's scribe. He
did hear about everything.
Detective Madsen? I saw a
guy hanging around earlier.
That's Len.
I think Amara
sucked out his soul.
I'll confess to all the
murders. Holy crap.
That way I can't get out.
We can't kill him 'cause
he hasn't done anything yet.
We don't wanna kill him.
We wanna save people.
Right. your new rules.
What can I do to help?
No. no. You just. uh.
sit there. take a breather.
- Watch some Netflix.
- Okay.
Besides. we got
bigger fish to fry.
Bye. Dean. I'll see you soon.
So. she says dating's gonna
break my focus for academics.
but that I'm allowed to
date over summer break.
How does that work?
Like. "Hi. I'm Goldie. I'm
only romantically available
"from June to August.
but wanna go steady?"
I hate her. Like. look at me.
I have to hang out by the
tracks just to get my snack on.
- She won't let you eat chips?
- Well. she'll let me.
But just so she can make
this face the whole time.
It's like. "Sorry. Mom. I can't
survive on menthol and diet soda
"like you can."
Mmm.
What? No.
Look. I hate my parents. too. Goldie.
They suck. But I got a curfew. Bye.
Fine. Bye.
Whoa.
Hey.
Where are your parents?
I don't have any parents.
I'm sorry. Um...
Are you okay? Do
you want something?
I want to be like you.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Midnight snack?
Don't think I don't know
what you've been up to.
You can try to deny it.
but the evidence is. well...
You told me to stop
feeding on your demons.
Well... I stopped
feeding on demons.
I thought I was clear.
Going out there? Where
they can see you? It's too risky.
I'm a growing
girl. I need to eat.
Actions have consequences
around here. Amara.
You've had the run of the Court.
We've seen what
you've made of it.
Believe me. this is going to hurt
me way more than it hurts you.
I'm sorry. my dear.
You're grounded.
You're strong...
But you need to
remember I'm stronger.
For now.
You said you had a good
feeling about that one.
Yeah. well. it seemed
like a solid lead. Dean.
Only a soulless psycho
would kill the family cat.
Yeah. unless the family cat
decides to take a nap in the dryer.
You know. we've been here since Monday and
still haven't found another legit victim.
Maybe Amara moved on or
stopped feeding altogether.
Well. finding her victims is still
the best shot we got at finding her.
Not actually true.
Oh. What. you think he's ready?
He's had a pretty rough go of it lately.
Which one of us hasn't?
It seems insane to leave our one
and only angel friend on the bench.
- I'll call him.
- Thank you.
We did this time. but it
literally doesn't matter.
Well. we're gonna get to all
the results in just a second.
We're gonna start with.
let's go back
to our first story.
Louis. Scilla and Edwin.
- Hi.
- Cas. how you doing. buddy?
I'm fine.
Find anything on Metatron?
Nothing on angel radio.
How long has it been
since you left the bunker?
Well. why would I leave? I've
got everything I need right here.
Wait. is th...
- Are you watching Jenny Jones?
- It's a rerun.
She's just about to
announce the paternity results.
You are the father.
Jenny. he is not
ready to be a father.
Okay. I thought you were going with
socially acceptable binge-watching.
You know. The Wire.
Game of Thrones.
Yeah. well. man can't
live on caviar alone. Dean.
Well. you sound
weird. okay? Bad weird.
- Now. I have been down this road before...
- What's up. Detective?
I have heard the siren
song from the idiot box.
and I'm telling you.
whatever you're looking for.
you won't find it in there.
So. do me a favor.
Turn off the TV. go
outside and get some air.
We're in the dark here. pal. I
need you back in the game. okay?
Yeah. I...
I got it.
Yeah. well. thanks for letting me
know. We'll head out there right now.
- You got it.
- What's up?
That was Detective Madsen.
Remember our friend Len?
Uh. Weird as hell. soulless.
took-the-rap-for-all-the-murders Len?
Yeah. He's dead.
Cass? Cass!
Don't do this.
Okay. this isn't you. it's
the spell. You can beat this!
I will end you!
No!
Don't!
I won't let you walk
out of this room.
Marco got one
of them last night.
A Len Fleischer.
Tell Marco to keep looking.
The last thing I need is one
of Amara's candy wrappers
blabbing to angels or hunters
about what. who. happened to them.
Where is everyone?
Oh. Our ranks have
been a bit thin. since...
Amara ate everybody.
I've got some fresh numbers
for you to go over before Court.
Soul projections.
they're not good.
We're down for the
quarter. which means that...
That door was supposed to
be locked and guarded 24/7.
Of course. sir.
I don't see a guard.
Uh. Right.
Must be a mix-up. We're
short-staffed and all. so...
Congratulations. You've been demoted.
No one goes in or out of that room.
Thought maybe a relative
of one of Len's victims.
But it doesn't feel
like a revenge killing.
Too clean.
Like an assassination.
- Detective?
- Excuse me.
- You smell that?
- Yeah.
Yeah. either the detective
needs to change his diet or...
Sulfur. Len was
killed by a demon.
Yeah. but why would a demon
run a hit on a guy with no soul?
That's like a Cracker
Jack without a prize.
Hands off. Deputy Doody!
- Who's the girl?
- Goldie Schmidtlapp.
Was a normal kid. snapped this morning.
tried to kill her mom with a frying pan.
First the ax murders.
then Len. now this?
We're gonna need
to talk to the kid.
That's four legs on four wheels.
Aw. That dog thinks it's people.
Up next. a very upsetting
story out of Omaha.
A downtown bar fight
escalated tragically last night.
and OWW-Two News brings
you an exclusive video of the event.
The footage you are about
to view is extremely graphic.
Efforts were made to
resuscitate the victim but...
Hey. Officer? Still haven't
gotten my phone call.
Do you think I could get
a pizza delivered in here?
- You're not the deputy.
- Nope.
The boss' daughter's been
making a mess in town.
and it's my job to clean it up.
Nothing personal.
Nice work. Goldie.
So. Crowley and Amara.
Huh.
Rise and shine. buttercup.
Now...
About what you were saying...
What's Crowley doing with Amara?
Don't know. Don't care.
Wouldn't tell you if I did.
Well. we already know
she's growing up fast.
Yeah. well. demon souls.
They do a body good.
The little moppet tore
through half my buds
before Crowley
put her on a diet.
She didn't like that.
Started sneaking out to get
her fill. You know how kids are.
But Daddy put his foot down.
- Where's he hiding her?
- Oh.
I'm happy to keep
gossiping with you boys. but...
You want actionable
intelligence?
Torture me if you want.
I know you'll just
kill me anyway.
Hmm.
Well. looks like a
stalemate to me.
I guess we'll go ahead
and kill him right now.
No. no. no. Dean. wait.
We can exorcise him.
- What?
- Save his meatsuit.
My two cents?
You exorcise me. let
me smoke on outta here?
I give you my word
not to tell Crowley.
Hey. you heard me. He's hardly
my favorite guy at the moment.
- I...
- Wait a second. Shut up.
Well. would you look at that?
There's no way his
suit survived that wound.
Mmm-mmm.
All right.
Crap.
- Hey.
- Where'd you ditch the body?
- School playground.
- Come on.
- Hospital parking lot.
- What do you got?
- Well. good news.
I was able to hack his phone.
Got the coordinates
of his call history.
I guess Crowley must have had
him tailing Amara or something.
'cause he was
at all three spots.
He was at the Lizzie Borden
house. where Len got his soul taken.
He was at the bar where
Sydney got her soul taken.
And he was here. where Goldie
said Amara approached her.
- Hmm. So. somewhere in there?
- Yeah. maybe.
But what I don't get is.
why would Crowley have
Amara on Earth
in the first place?
I mean. wouldn't it be
smarter to keep her in Hell?
Yeah. but then he'd have to spend
more time there. and he hates that place.
Oh. right.
I keep forgetting about you
and Crowley's summer of love.
I'm not seeing much inside
this radius that he'd like better.
- I mean. you got farms. you got swamps...
- Yeah.
- This P.O.I.? What's that?
- Point of interest.
I know what it... What is it?
- Well. let's find out.
- Yeah.
The Needham Asylum.
Decommissioned in '63.
Sound like Crowley's
kind of place to you?
What are you looking at?
Still learning all you
can about the world?
If nonsensical slogans attached to
idiotic pictures of domestic animals
- counts as the world.
- Excuse me?
Memes.
Ah.
Look. I know. to
you. my rules seem...
Unfair. arbitrary.
As though I'm doing
all this just to hurt you.
I don't care why
you do anything.
I just want you to know
that I'm not a monster.
Jervis?
I can't have you eating
whatever. whenever.
however much you want.
I thought you might
appreciate a little snack.
I'm not hungry.
I'll leave you to your memes.
I have no idea
what I'm doing here.
Not a bleeding clue.
Moment to moment. what makes
you happy. what will set you off?
How to even begin to
forge a connection with you.
But what I do know is
you're growing so fast.
And it terrifies me.
I bet.
You only want me
for the power I'll wield.
And you know. soon enough.
I won't need you anymore.
So. we're really
gonna do this? Now?
Hell. yeah.
I've been looking for a
chance to get back at Crowley
ever since that crap he
pulled in Cedar Rapids.
Especially now that I know he tricked
me and made off with The Darkness.
No. that's not what I meant.
We're going in to kill Amara.
Are you ready for that?
Why wouldn't I be?
Because we don't know the
first thing about her. Dean.
We don't know her powers. We
don't know how to take her down.
Hell. you know what? We don't
even know if she can be killed.
I know. But she's too
big of a threat to wait.
I say we go in there and we
hit her with everything we got.
You have tremendous power
and soon. you'll have even more.
But I have something you lack.
Wisdom. Experience.
I helped put Lucifer
back in his cage.
I rose through the ranks
of Hell. defeated all comers.
to claim the throne.
And. a few minor setbacks
aside. I'm still here.
I don't know how to impart what
I've learned to you. how to teach you.
And at the rate
that you're growing.
I'll probably never get
the chance to figure it out.
Perhaps you don't
need my tutelage.
But I believe. deep
down in my gut.
I have something to offer you.
if you just give me the chance.
What are you asking for?
Time.
Slow down.
Play by my rules for
just a little bit longer.
You give me your patience.
I'll give you my protection.
Until you decide you
don't need it anymore.
Okay.
Oh. This is good.
A night-leader
if ever I saw one.
This is gonna fetch
me 500. minimum.
I. uh...
I know 500 sounds like
plenty. but with my overhead?
Daddy's got to eat.
Oh. Come on!
Help. Please.
I'm sorry. buddy. You
live. there's no story.
Ugh...
You know. there was a time...
I could have brought you back from
the brink with a snap of my fingers.
Not that I would have.
But I'm not that guy anymore.
I can't save you.
I can.
- How did you find me?
- Same way you found him.
Scoured the police scanners.
got ahead of the authorities.
What was that?
What?
Look. a real live
angel. caught on tape?
That is way better than
some random homicide.
Hey!
Do you have any
idea how much stuff
I had to steal and then
pawn to pay for that?
No guards at the perimeter?
Looks like there are no
guards at the door. either.
You think this is
the right place. still?
Well. warding sigils.
And for the humans...
Look at this. a padlock you'd
find on a middle-school locker.
- Cocky son of a bitch.
- Dean. external security may be lax.
but we still don't know how many
demons we're gonna face inside.
Well. let's find out.
Turn to the graph
at the bottom of 27
and you'll see a nearly 40%
decrease in soul collections
in the Pacific Northwest
over the past three years.
An unexpected consequence
of legalized marijuana?
Some analysts think so.
Others are not quite so sure...
Okay. Marv.
You're picking pockets.
leaving a man to die...
I don't know what I expected.
but this is disappointing.
One to talk.
You chose the life
of a wage slave.
slinging Slurpees
for what? A month?
I am in it to win it.
I was at zero when
you took my grace.
Hiding from angels.
not a cent to my name.
But I found my calling.
And I pulled myself up by my
bootstraps and started a business.
And you know. my
story has only just begun.
What story is that?
You're preying like a
vulture on human tragedy.
Oh. jeez.
Castiel.
What century are you in?
Religion is dead!
The novel? Deader.
You think I'm ashamed for
dealing in fleeting visual sensation?
In GIF-length glimpses of
horror. waste. and degradation?
No!
I just caught up with the times!
Reality is the great
literature of our era.
and I am out there. on the streets.
every single night. capturing it.
- I am reality's author...
- Oh. Save your story.
It is not what I came for.
Oh.
So. straight to business.
You want the Demon Tablet?
Well. you're not gonna get it.
I have hidden it very carefully in a
place where you and your friends...
You hid it under your mattress.
The TV station gave me your
address and I checked the place out.
You realize you have bedbugs?
You broke into my apartment?
What do you know
about The Darkness?
The band?
Okay.
Uh...
Sometimes. during
late-night writing sessions.
when God was deep in his cups.
he may have let slip
a few choice words.
But I don't have
to tell you anything.
Are you forgetting?
You are human now. And I
could crush you like a bug.
Could.
But you won't.
You think I didn't notice?
You are broken. Castiel.
You were always a
bit of a nancy. but this?
You have gone full wuss.
I don't know what it
was that happened.
but whatever it was.
you are scarred deep.
Paralyzed by trauma. by fear.
I mean. look at you.
You can't even hit me.
It's not fear.
Hey. idiot! Ándale!
That's Spanish for
"Get your ass over here."
- Do you think I've been paying your...
- Sir?
Astronomical bar tabs
for the past five weeks
so you can sleep past
noon with last night's skank?
Well. Dean...
Is that him?
You know what? Go.
Take her out. I got 'em.
I knew you'd come.
I'm sorry. Amara.
For what?
What I have to do.
Hello. Dean.
My girl is growing up.
Should have known it wouldn't be long
before the boys came sniffing around.
What do you want
with her. Crowley?
What do you think. you can use
her? Control her? You're an idiot.
I'm not trying to control her.
I'm helping her to realize
her fullest potential.
Do you know how
disturbing it was
to realize that I couldn't
bring myself to kill you?
I've had tons of
chances over the years.
Some you don't even
know about. But still...
I made my peace with it.
Embraced my softer side.
Learned to accept that there was just
too much going on between you and I.
Bromance.
But you know what?
I think I am gonna
kill you today.
I feel different. somehow.
Ready. What can I say?
Fatherhood changes a man.
The Darkness.
What do you know?
Okay.
So I misjudged.
You're not scared. You're mad.
And I get it.
I mean. it must suck.
being everyone's tool.
Manipulated and used.
By the angels. By your
enemies. By your fr...
You thought if you
could get your grace back.
it would help fix
you. But it hasn't.
The Darkness.
Why. Amara?
I thought we had
an understanding.
Yeah. Your promise
to protect me.
And then. hours later. I'm
assaulted in my own room.
Don't seem terribly upset by it.
That's not the point.
I've decided I don't
need your protection.
And I certainly don't
need your captivity.
I'm done.
You trying out some
kind of no-kill policy?
Who do you have to thank for
how angry you are? How lost?
You're welcome.
A hunter. You of all
people should know.
Pacifism doesn't pay.
Go on. Castiel. End me.
No.
All right. Two out of three.
Dean!
It's time.
Time for you to blink your tired ass
back to your throne and lick your wounds.
I'll spare your life
on one condition.
Safe passage for Dean.
out of here. after I'm gone.
Yes!
Good.
Now.
Get out of my room.
Oh. Please. Castiel.
Help me.
You said you were happy.
Your bootstraps.
I was faking it.
I mean...
I thought. "How
hard could it be?"
You won't.
You can't.
Can't take anymore.
Not a single human day.
I mean...
The indignities.
they just don't stop.
They...
Making my rent and
keeping my phone charged.
Hemorrhoids.
You were right. Metatron.
I am sick of having
my strings pulled.
Which is why I won't let you
manipulate me into letting you off easy.
Oh...
Tell me about The Darkness.
Tell me.
What is happening
here. between us?
You save me. I save you.
Why?
You were the first thing
I saw when I was freed.
And it had been so long.
Maybe that's it.
My first experience of...
His creation.
You can't help but
represent that for me.
The sweet triumph and the even
sweeter folly of what He's wrought.
There's no fighting it.
I'm fascinated.
The truth.
It'd make the Bible-thumpers'
heads explode.
I mean. they want
their God to be a...
You know. a finger-snapping.
all-powerful Creator. you know?
They want magic.
Mary Poppins.
But what he did?
Creation?
That took work.
It took sacrifice.
In order to create the world.
God had to give up the
only thing he'd ever known.
He had to betray and sacrifice
his only kin.
The Darkness.
His sister.
It's been great seeing
you again. Dean.
But it's time for me to go.
There's a whole world
out there for me to explore.
And I can practically taste it.
Soon. I'll be strong enough
to do what I came here to do.
What's that?
Settle an old score.
The oldest score.
Told ya.
Look. Cass. I'm as glad as anyone
that Stella got her groove back. okay?
But you let Metatron go?
Dean. How many times are
you going to repeat that question?
I'm gonna say it again!
You let Metatron go!
He's not going anywhere.
If he makes a move. if he
draws the slightest attention.
the full force of angel-kind
will snuff him out.
Look. you...
Neither of you saw
him. He is a human.
And a pitiable one at that.
He's not a threat to us.
Look. I mean. I
put him in traction.
Guys. bigger fish to fry.
here. Amara is in the wind.
Yeah. God's freaking sister.
You said you were close.
Dean. How'd she get away?
I'm sorry. what part of
"God's freaking sister"
did you not understand? She
overpowered me. End of story.
What's our plan. here. fellas?
You said you got everything
you could out of Metatron. right?
So. where on Earth are we gonna
find an answer on how to stop her?
I don't suppose God's decided to
share any wisdom on the matter?
I'll look into the lore.
ENGLISH -SDH
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm